There is a woman here.
There is a spirit of suicide.
Anytime this spirit come upon you,
you begin to look for knife; cutlery.
Anywhere you could find it, you begin to look.
Dark in complexion.
Many are the times you would find a knife,
you want to kill yourself.
This is the spirit of suicide.
Please, come out.
Any time this spirit come upon you....
they want to use you to commit murder.
So that you can be sentenced to life imprisonment.
What a beautiful woman, come out.
Jesus loves you.
Hallelujah.
{The woman comes forward to confirm
the prophecy of the man of God.
concerning the spirit of suicide.}
There is a spirit in you and when
the spirit comes upon you,
you begin to look for knife; cutlery.
Its true sir.
You want to commit suicide,
there was a time you ran to the
kitchen and carried knife.
Yes sir.
And you were running, you wanted to kill;
to slaughter yourself.
Yes sir, it is true, and like snake running round my head.
Look at her, what a beautiful woman.
satan wants just to destroy this woman.
There are two things satan
wants to do in your life,
either you kill yourself or kill somebody
so that you can be sentenced to life imprisonment.
or you kill yourself, they don't want you in circulation.
Yes sir, its true sir.
Please deliver me sir.
{That is the woman undergoing deliverance.
the man of God gave a prophetic message.
Anytime the spirit comes upon her she will be looking for cutlery..}
Out!
{to kill herself or anybody around her
That there are two things that
wants to happen to her,
either she kills herself because
they don't want her in circulation
or she kills someone around.}
Out!
In the mighty name of Jesus.
Stand up and come here!
Stand up!
Come here!
We are commanding the spirit anywhere
it is hiding; its going and coming out.
But it should come now.
Come here!
Out!
You see the face, that is what normally
happen when she carry knife.
Can you see the face has changed?
This is exactly what happens,
Anytime she carry the knife.
This is the face she bare.
Can you see, when she is delivered
the face will come down to normal.
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command that spirit, out!
Out!
He's gone.
Thank you Jesus!
I am free!
Do you see the face is coming back now.
Now, she's free.
[clapping]
Praise the Lord!
My name is Blessing
I am from Abuja state, Nigeria.
I was in the church last week when the
man of God prophesied to me
that i have a spirit of suicide which was very true.
Each time I am at home, I really want to thank God.
I would be feeling a movement like
a snake moving over my body
I couldn't sleep at night, I would be
very aggressive.
Each time I was at home, I would go to the length
where I would want to kill my self.
My parents and husband would hold me.
I hated everything around me, including my children
At night I couldn't sleep.
My whole body would be hot and burning me.
I couldn't sleep at night.
But when the Man of God prayed for me,
he delivered me.
I am free, I can sleep like a baby.
The snake movement in my body is no more there.
I give God the glory, I give Him all the adoration.
[Clapping.]
I am okay, I don't have the spirit of suicide.
In fact, I am very, very okay.
[clapping]
I want to advice people, if anyone
is having the suicide spirit,
they should come to SCOAN and they
should not be shy about it.
Let them put their hope in God and
God will surely deliver them.
[clapping]